There are not many videos that I do
that come with a warning.
But if you continue to watch this video,
it could cost you thousands of dollars.
There is something called an Eight Sleep.
Now, I'm not here to sell it to you.
I'm here to tell you about how genius the
marketing is.
And in this video,
we're going to look through some very
sneaky tactics they use
that we can admire
and implement into our own businesses.
Very simply, Eight Sleep
is a mattress cover.
You put it on your mattress.
I don't know about you, I'm very warm,
my missus is very cold.
We argue about the air con.
When the arrival of my new son came,
she said, "If you
keep the air con on the temperature you
like to sleep with, he will freeze to
death." So we considered the Eight Sleep.
This means that throughout the night,
as I'm asleep,
the mattress wicks away heat
when I get too hot,
and then warms me up when I get too cold.
It checks out my heart rate variability,
my breathing rate.
It even gives me a sleep score
when I wake up. Now,
here's the crazy thing.
This mattress topper costs thousands of
dollars.
So you decide to head over to the Eight
Sleep website, and as soon as you get on
there, oh yeah, I'm in Australia. What
is that pop-up that's just occurred?
"Limited time. A surprise
is waiting for you. What
is your main sleep challenge?
I feel hot or cold." Right there and then,
we have seen the landing
page turn into a squeeze page very
quickly.
"Enter your email to unlock your
surprise." One of the things
that we like to do in
YouTube is try and create an itch
that needs to be scratched.
Now if this said,
"Join my newsletter," we'd be gone.
We'd be running out of here.
"Enter your email to unlock your
surprise." My surprise? What could
that be?
Now, what I want you all to do
is to actually sign up to Eight Sleep's
emails,
just so you can get a taste of email
marketing, because I'm always saying,
"Hey, click the link in the description,
get my 30-day email autoresponder." But
I'm actually saying,
go look at this amazing company that's got
some of the best
marketing in the world,
and look how aggressive they try
and sell you.
Some of you out there think
that an email a day is too aggressive.
However,
if there's something good to be sold,
and your sleep is going to get
better, and your life is going to improve,
can you actually market too hard to
someone whose life you want to improve?
This, again,
is a perfectly curated landing page.
"Nights that fuel your best days." What an
amazing statement.
"Turn any bed into the ultimate sleeping
experience." Ever since having an Eight
Sleep,
and I've used one for about a year
and a half now, I can go stay in the
nicest hotels. Vegas, New York, LA,
doesn't matter.
Do you know what I suffer with? Hotness.
Until an Eight Sleep
is a staple in a five-star hotel,
it's one of them things that
when you discover it, it ruins your life.
A bit like when you're watching a movie
and you're thinking, "Where is the
microphone?" Then you realize the lips
are out of sync.
A bit like when you have a posh wank at
home and use coconut oil.
So every landing page should be a perfect
scrolling experience.
As I'm scrolling down,
"The ultimate sleep solution." Every
single word here is
thought out very carefully.
I'm now being shown what it does.
And again, for any of you
that watched my content before,
I like to say that your
landing page should say what it is,
what I get, why I need it,
how much it costs,
how to buy,
with a little sprinkle of why to trust
you.
So I do have the mattress
that sits you up in bed.
Apart from my hernia surgery,
never needed it.
"Transform any bed with the pod." Now this
is the amazing part.
"Try risk-free for 30 nights." This
is where I was hit in a
crossroads, because I was thinking,
I can't spend 3,500 US dollars on a
mattress
cover. I was considering it,
thinking maybe I'll make it a YouTube
video.
Maybe I'll write off the cost because I'm
doing a video about it.
But then when it goes try it risk-free,
I'm always saying money-back guarantee,
right? This is amazing. For you,
a lot of people out there,
a money-back guarantee
might means that you do a little bit of
work for someone,
and then they turn out to
be a shit client,
and you send them the money back.
Eight Sleep is going to send you a device
that probably cost them hundreds, if not
thousands of dollars, they have to ship.
And trust me, the case
is about 80 kilograms of stuff they've
shipped to your
house. They are that confident
that their mattress cover
is going to blow your
mind and revolutionize your sleep forever.
They're going to send you a small human
body's worth of packages to
your house, and if you return it,
they're going to be stumped with a product
that
potentially someone slept on for a few
weeks, so I very much doubt they're
reselling it. "Experience the pod at home.
If it's not the perfect fit,
return it for a refund." This is my
perfect marketing. If Eight Sleep
was open to investment, I'd invest in
it. And everywhere we go down the page,
there's opportunities to buy, to shop now.
I like the fact that we're going from
light mode to dark mode.
For any of you on your landing pages,
I'm a big fan at the moment of a dark
screen
with light text. I find it easier to read.
And there's just frequent buttons
that say Shop Now.
There are not many things in my life
that I simp over, but my Eight Sleep
is one of
them. Anyone in your life that you love,
that's amazing to you, and you're not sure
what to get them, get them this.
Just be ready for the price.
Pod 4 Ultra, 7,000 Aussie dollars.
About 3,500 US, which is crazy,
but think of it this way.
One big trip away with your partner to
Dubai, or go somewhere all-inclusive,
you're
probably spending similar money on a big
holiday.
So I'm saying don't go on holiday.
Instead, get yourself an Eight Sleep and
revolutionize sleep forever.
And I know what you're going to think
here, right?
There is a monthly recurring membership to
use your mattress and your
bed.
And I know that seems pretty
Machiavellian, but it's amazing.
They don't pay me to say this.
I am an Eight Sleep convert.
But the message I'm trying to drive home
today is, look to other businesses in
completely different niches
and look what's happening here.
We have marketing, content,
social media ambassadors, whatever.
The second you land on the website,
first thing they go for
is your email address,
because they know if you leave,
you're probably not coming back,
so they want to
have contact with you. The landing page
is a well-curated, thought-out story about
the benefits, what it is, why you get.
The massive thing that they do here
is why to trust them.
Those that get the emails,
you'll start to see an aggressive email
marketing
campaign. And also, those of you
that actually buy this
and remortgage your house
to have a good night's sleep,
you will credit me with being the legend
that put you
onto it. Six months from now,
you're going to go,
"James." I'm going to go, "You
like the content?" You go, "No, mate.
You waffle too much.
But thanks for the mattress
recommendation.
You live good forever." Sweet.
Come in for my email address again.
Makes me bloody proud to see.
Eight Sleep, well done.
Fantastic marketing.
You got a customer for life.
And look at that.
Selling thousands of dollars of products
with recurring
revenue,
and not once did they need to get you on
the phone to sell you it.
Wonderful. And if you think it
was refreshing for me to talk about
someone else's
business and not myself for a video, well,
check out this one where I'm talking
about one of my mentors who
was so inspirational to me
and my business that I had
to steal ideas from him.
And I still steal from him to this very
day.
Check out that. Well,
there'll be links in the description.
I've got to go, Declan.
I've got to go. I'm going training.
I will see you later.
Remember what I said.
Get that fucking edit done.
Whoa. Do you want the Teller one first
or this one?
You finish the Teller one first.
Okay.
But the Eight Sleep one,
I reckon we can leverage people
that have heard of Eight
Sleep but never heard of us,
then we can get their money.
So bring them in.
"Oh, Eight Sleep,
I've been thinking about that." Really?
We get them.
They'll check out the links in the bio.
Cashish, Declan, cashish.
Good idea.
Not for you. I'll get a lot,
but you can maybe get a little bit of it.
Whatever I make, you can have a tiny bit.
All right?
See you in a bit.
See you in
a bit, mate. [car revving]
Dickhead